Guide to the Delta Gamma, Chi chapter records, 1874-2013
Delta Gamma, Chi chapter records,
- Series IV. The Anchora of Delta Gamma
  - Volume LXIX, November 1952 - Summer 1953 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIX, Number 3, March 1953 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXIX, Number 4, Summer 1953 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXX, Fall 1953 - Summer 1954 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXX, Number 1, Fall 1953 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXX, Number 2, Winter 1953 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXX, Number 3, Spring 1954 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXX, Number 4, Summer 1954 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXI, Fall 1954 - Summer 1955 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXI, Number 1, Fall 1954 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXI, Number 2, Winter 1954 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXI, Number 3, Spring 1955 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXI, Number 4, Summer 1955 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXII, Fall 1955 - Summer 1956 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXII, Number 1, Fall 1955 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXII, Number 2, Winter 1955 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXII, Number 3, Spring 1956 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXII, Number 4, Summer 1956 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXIV, Fall 1957 - Summer 1958 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIV, Number 1, Fall 1957 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIV, Number 2, Winter 1957 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIV, Number 3, Spring 1958 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIV, Number 4, Summer 1958 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXVI, Fall 1959 - Summer 1960 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVI, Number 1, Fall 1959 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVI, Number 2, Winter 1959 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVI, Number 3, Spring 1960 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVI, Number 4, Summer 1960 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXVII, Fall 1960 - Summer 1961 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVII, Number 1, Fall 1960 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVII, Number 2, Winter 1960 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVII, Number 3, Spring 1961 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVII, Number 4, Summer 1961 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXVIII, Fall 1961 - Summer 1962 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVIII, Number 1, Fall 1961 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVIII, Number 2, Winter 1961 (Box 4)
      Incorrectly published as issue number 1.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVIII, Number 3, Spring 1962 (Box 4)
      Incorrectly published as issue number 2.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXVIII, Number 4, Summer 1962 (Box 4)
      Incorrectly published as issue number 3.
  - Volume LXXIX, Fall 1962 - Summer 1963 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIX, Number 1, Fall 1962 (Box 4)
      Incorrectly published as Volume LXXVIII issue number 4.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIX, Number 2, Winter 1962 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIX, Number 3, Spring 1963 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXIX, Number 4, Summer 1963 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXX, Fall 1963 - Summer 1964 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXX, Number 1, Fall 1963 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXX, Number 2, Winter 1963 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXX, Number 3, Spring 1964 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXX, Number 4, Summer 1964 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXI, Fall 1964 - Summer 1965 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXI, Number 1, Fall 1964 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXI, Number 2, Winter 1964 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXI, Number 3, Spring 1965 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXI, Number 4, Summer 1965 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXII, Fall 1965 - Summer 1966 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXII, Number 1, Fall 1965 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXII, Number 2, Winter 1965 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXII, Number 3, Spring 1966 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXII, Number 4, Summer 1966 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXIII, Fall 1966 - Summer 1967 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIII, Number 1, Fall 1966 (Box 4)
      Missing cover, see additional loose copy.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIII, Number 1, Fall 1966 (Box 4)
      Loose issue not bound within this set.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIII, Number 2, Winter 1966 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIII, Number 3, Spring 1967 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIII, Number 4, Summer 1967 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXIV, Fall 1967 - Summer 1968 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIV, Number 1, Fall 1967 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIV, Number 2, Winter 1967 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIV, Number 3, Spring 1968 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIV, Number 4, Summer 1968 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXV, Fall 1968 - Summer 1969 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXV, Number 1, Fall 1968 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXV, Number 2, Winter 1968 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXV, Number 3, Spring 1969 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXV, Number 4, Summer 1969 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXVI, Fall 1969 - Summer 1970 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVI, Number 1, Fall 1969 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVI, Number 2, Winter 1969 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVI, Number 3, Spring 1970 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVI, Number 4, Summer 1970 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXVII, Fall 1970 - Summer 1971 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVII, Number 1, Fall 1970 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVII, Number 2, Winter 1970 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVII, Number 3, Spring 1971 (Box 4)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXVII, Number 4, Summer 1971 (Box 4)
  - Volume LXXXIX, Fall 1972 - Winter 1973 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIX, Number 1, Fall 1972 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIX, Number 2, Winter 1972 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIX, Number 3, Spring 1973 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIX, Number 4, Summer 1973 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIX, Number 5, Fall 1973 (Box 5)
      Numbering system changes for volume and issue number.
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIX, Number 6, Winter 1973 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume LXXXIX, Number 6, Winter 1973 (Box 4)
  - Volumes C - CI, Spring 1984 - Winter 1985 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume C, Number 1, Spring 1984 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume C, Number 2, Summer 1984 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume C, Number 3, Fall 1984 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume C, Number 4, Winter 1984 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume CI, Number 1, Spring 1985 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume CI, Number 2, Summer 1985 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume CI, Number 3, Fall 1985 (Box 5)
    - The Anchora of Delta Gamma, Volume CI, Number 4, Winter 1985 (Box 5)
- Series V. Additional Publications
  - First Catalogue of the Delta Gamma Fraternity, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Heavily annotated with member names from the late 1800s.
  - An Historical Sketch of the Delta Gamma Fraternity, 1874-1934, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Twenty-first Convention of Delta Gamma, June 26-30, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Twenty-second Convention of Delta Gamma, June 23-28, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - The Shield of Delta Gamma, First Edition, 1968 (Box 5)
  - The Shield of Delta Gamma, Second Edition, 1968 (Box 5)
  - The Shield of Delta Gamma, Third Edition, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Delta Gamma History, 1873-1945, 1945 (Box 5)
    Reprint of the January 1945 Anchora Volume LXI Number 2.
  - A History of Delta Gamma, Sixth Edition, 1873-1966, 1966 (Box 5)
    Reprint of the Fall 1966 Anchora Volume LXXXIII Number 1.
  - A History of Delta Gamma, Seventh Edition, 1873-1973, 1973 (Box 5)
    Reprint of the Winter 1973 Anchora Volume XC Number 2.